[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (3 + 6 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "14",
        "15",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 8 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "options": [
        "41",
        "39",
        "38",
        "40"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 8 \u00d7 4) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "12",
        "11",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (6 + 3 \u00d7 6) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "7",
        "9",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (7 + 6 \u00d7 2) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "8",
        "7",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 5 \u00d7 5) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "9",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "9",
        "11",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (4 + 2 \u00d7 9) \u00f7 3?",
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "9",
        "6",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (8 + 10 \u00d7 7) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "options": [
        "41",
        "39",
        "40",
        "38"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (10 + 4 \u00d7 7) \u00f7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "38",
      "options": [
        "38",
        "37",
        "40",
        "39"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of (2 + 6 \u00d7 1) \u00f7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "4",
        "6",
        "5"
      ]
    }
]